What is your earliest memory?
你最早的记忆是什么呢？
For me, I have a hazy recollection of standing in a leafy garden surrounded by silver birch trees when I was four years old.
对我来说，我有一段模糊的回忆，那是在我四岁的时候，站在一个绿树成荫的花园里，周围环绕着白桦树。
I'm around average: some people remember events as far back as two years old, while for others, things seem patchy until seven or eight.
我的情况大概处于平均水平：有些人能记得早在两岁时发生的事情，而对另一些人来说，在七岁或八岁之前，记忆似乎是不很可靠的。
But what is consistent is that no one can remember their own birth or very early infancy.
但一致的是，没有人能记得自己的出生或非常早期的婴儿时期。
And even after the first memory, most of us only have a sporadic collection of fleeting, flickering mental images until much later in childhood.
而且即使有了最初的记忆，我们中的大多数人也只是有一些零星的、短暂的、忽隐忽现的脑海中的画面，直到童年的很晚时候才有所改变。
The phenomenon is known as 'childhood amnesia', a term coined by the father of psychoanalysis, Sigmund Freud.
这种现象被称为“童年失忆症”，这是由精神分析之父西格蒙德·弗洛伊德创造的一个术语。
So, what's going on here?
那么，这里到底是怎么回事呢？
Babies are, writes Zaria Gorvett for BBC Future, "sponges for new information, forming 700 new neural connections every second and wielding language-learning skills to make the most accomplished polyglot green with envy."
扎里亚·戈尔维特为BBC未来栏目撰文写道，婴儿是“吸收新信息的海绵，每秒形成700个新的神经连接，并且运用语言学习技能，让最有成就的通晓多种语言的人都炉火中烧”。
And it's precisely this rapid mental development that causes the problem, according to a study by the University of Toronto in 2014.
根据多伦多大学2014年的一项研究，恰恰是这种快速的智力发展导致了这个问题。
It found that the high rate of infant brain cell production could increase forgetfulness, because new cells interfere with existing mental circuits.
研究发现，婴儿脑细胞的高生成率可能会增加健忘的情况，因为新细胞会干扰现有的大脑神经回路。
Another possible explanation is that the part of the brain that stores memories, the hippocampus, is not fully formed until around 18 months.
另一个可能的解释是，大脑中储存记忆的部分，即海马体，直到大约18个月大时才完全发育成型。
Identity is also important: tests show infants don't recognise themselves in the mirror until they are around two years old.
身份（自我）认知也很重要：测试表明，婴儿直到大约两岁时才会在镜子中认出自己。
Finally, there's the question of how accurate our early memories are at all.
最后，还有一个问题，那就是我们早期的记忆到底有多准确。
"People can pick up suggestions and begin to visualise them - they become like memories," psychologist Elizabeth Loftus told the BBC.
“人们可以接受暗示，并开始想象这些暗示——它们就变得像记忆一样。”心理学家伊丽莎白·洛夫特斯告诉BBC。
Are our cherished first memories really just family stories?
我们珍视的最初记忆真的只是家庭故事吗？